Congratulations on making it to the end of this short course
祝贺你在这个短期课程中走到了最后
In summary, in this short course
综上所述，在这个短课程中
you've learned about two key principles for prompting
你已经了解了提示的两个关键原则
right clearance for specific instructions and when it's appropriate
正确且清晰的描述具体指示，以及知道什么时候使用
give the model time to think
给予模型思考的时间
You also learned about iterative prompt development and how
你还了解了迭代提示的发展以及如何
having a process to get to the prompt is right for your application is key
有一个过程来获得适合你的应用的提示是关键
And we went through a few capabilities of
我们还学习了一些大语言模型的功能
large language models that are useful for many applications
这些功能对许多应用是有用的
specifically summarizing, inferring, transforming, and expanding
特别是总结、推理、转换和扩展
And you also saw how to build a custom chatbot
你还看到了如何建立一个定制的聊天机器人
That was a lot that you learned in just one short course
在短短的课程中，你学到了很多东西
and I hope you enjoyed going through these materials
我希望你喜欢阅读这些材料
We hope you'll come up with some ideas for
我们希望你能想出一些想法
applications that you can build yourself now
我们希望你能想出一些可以自己构建的应用
And please go try this out and let us know what you come up with
并请你去尝试一下，让我们知道你想出了什么
No application is too small
任何应用都不小
It's fine to start with something that's kind of
从一些很小的项目开始也是可以的
a very small project with maybe a little bit of utility
一个非常小的项目，也许实用
or maybe it's not even useful at all
也可能毫无用处
It's just something fun
这只是一些有趣的东西
Yeah. And I find playing with these models actually really fun
是的。我发现玩这些模型非常有趣
So go play with it
所以放心去玩吧
Yeah, I agree. It's a good
是的，我同意。从我的经验来看
a good weekend activity, speaking from experience
这是一个很好的周末活动
And just, you know
而且，你可以通过第一个项目获得的经验教训
please use the learnings from your first project to build a better second project
来构建第二个更好的项目
and you know, maybe even a better third project, so on
甚至可能是更好的第三个项目，等等
That's kind of how I have kind of grown over time using these models myself as well
这就是我自己使用这些模型逐渐成长的方式
Or if you have an idea for a bigger project already, just, just go for it
或者如果你已经有了一个更大的项目想法，就去做吧
And, you know, as a reminder
作为一个提醒
these kind of large language models are a very powerful technology
这些大语言模型是一种非常强大的技术
So it kind of goes without saying that we ask you to use them responsibly
所以不言而喻，我们要求你负责任地使用它们
and please only build things that will have a positive impact
请只建立会产生积极影响的东西
Yeah, fully agree. I think in this age
是的，完全同意。我认为在这个时代
people that build AI systems can have a huge impact on others
建立AI系统的人可以对其他人产生巨大的影响
So it's more important than ever that all of us only use these tools responsibly
因此，我们所有人都要负责任地使用这些工具，这一点比以往任何时候都重要
And I think building large language model-based applications
我认为建立基于大语言模型的应用程序
is just a very exciting and growing field right now
是一个非常令人兴奋和不断增长的领域
And now that you've finished this course
现在你已经完成了这个课程
I think you now have a wealth of knowledge to let
我想你现在已经有了丰富的知识
you build things that few people today know how to
可以让你构建少数人知道如何构建的东西
So I hope you also help us to spread the word and encourage others to take this course too
与此同时，我希望你也能帮助我们传播信息，鼓励其他人也参加这个课程
In closing, I hope you had fun doing this course
最后，我希望你在做这个课程时很开心
and I want to thank you for finishing this course
同时也感谢你能完成这个课程
and both Isa and I look forward to hearing about the amazing things that you've built
Isa和我都期待着听到你所建立的惊人的东西